xtemos.com 2019-09-07

# Privacy Policy - XTemos

Our website address is: [https://xtemos.com](https://xtemos.com/).

Thank you for visiting XTemos Studio. We are a company, creating products to enhance your website building experience. Please read this Privacy Policy, providing consent to document in order to have permission to use our services.

### WHAT PERSONAL DATA WE COLLECT AND WHY WE COLLECT IT

If you register on our website, we store your chosen username and your email address and any additional personal information added to your user profile. You can see, edit, or delete your personal information at any time (except changing your username). Website administrators can also see and edit this information.

To receive product support, you have to register one or more Envato purchase codes on our site. These purchase codes will be stored together with support expiration dates and your user data. This is required for us to provide you with product support and other customer services.

If you have registered on our site and have a valid support account, you can submit support tickets for assistance via our support forum. Only the data you explicitly provided is stored, and you are asked for consent, each time you want to create a new support topic.

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

Information submitted through the contact form on our site is sent to our company email, hosted by Gmail. Google adheres to the EU/US “Privacy Shield” policy and you can find more information about this here: [Google Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy/frameworks).

These submissions are only kept for customer service purposes they are never used for marketing purposes or shared with third parties.

We use Google Analytics on our site for anonymous reporting of site usage. So, no personalized data is stored. If you would like to opt-out of Google Analytics monitoring your behavior on our site please use this link: [Google Analytics Opt-out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

9. EMBEDDED CONTENT FROM OTHER WEBSITES 

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

10. HOW LONG WE RETAIN YOUR DATA 

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

11. WHAT RIGHTS YOU HAVE OVER YOUR DATA 

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

12. WHERE WE SEND YOUR DATA 

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
